SUMMARY

I hold a Master's degree in Artificial Intelligence and a Bachelor's degree in Electronics Engineering with a specialization in computer vision, real-time systems, and robotics. My primary interest lies in developing advanced technologies that enhance the quality of life for individuals. I focus on task automation to minimize human time spent on repetitive tasks, enabling them to concentrate on delivering genuine value.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Jul 2021 - Currently | Amsterdam (Netherlands)

Development of data acquisition system for new generation microscope.
 Using C++17/20.



- Development of onnxruntime based imaging inference libraries.
- Maintenance, upgrade and creation of **conan** recipes for build system.
- Imaging acquisition algorithms. Using **OpenCV**, **tensorflow**.
- Prototyping of real-time imaging acquisition systems for high force environments.
 Using FFmpeg, OpenCV, mbedOS, C++, Python, electronics circuits.

AI LEAD Jan 2021 - Jul 2021 | Remote (Netherlands)

- Incorporation of Emotion Research Lab computer vision technology to Uniphore's during acquisition phase.
- Deployment of a highly scalable Deep learning platform for video processing in real-time.



Al LEAD Jan 2019 - Jan 2021 | Valencia (Spain), Remote (Netherlands)

- Responsible of AI technology and development.
- Develop several products up to the acquisition of the company from a 100M\$ Series C company.
- Deployment of a highly scalable Deep learning platform for video processing in the cloud using AWS ECS.
- Emotion recognition pipeline implementation in C++ and Tensorflow.
- Development of a **multi-platform** automatic release for Windows, Linux (CPU, GPU) and **Jetson** platform.
- Core library migration from C++98 to C++14.

E M O T I O N

COMPUTER VISION DEVELOPER Oct 2018 - Dec 2018 | Rome (Italy)

- Research of solutions for the task of real time depth estimation from monocular images. GANs and VAEs were the developed proofs of concepts.
- Development done inside a collaboration program between PI School and Cisco.

COMPUTER VISION DEVELOPER Ago 2017 - Oct 2018 | Vigo (Spain)

- Development and fine-tuning of object detection pipelines for embedded devices deployment based on Deep Learning (Caffe and Tensorflow).
- R&D of pipelines focusing in fast inference (Intel Movidius, TensorRT).
- Development of a system for vehicles and pedestrian counting and tracking in real-time. (Jetson Board, C++14)
- Development of a semi-automated development and testing suite for deep learning models to decrease the time between experiments.





JUNIOR CONSULTANT Feb 2016 - Feb 2017 | Valencia (Spain)

Full stack web development.

Keywords: Java, Spring, Hibernate, ExtJS and Oracle RDBMS.



DEVELOPER Jun 2015 - Feb 2016 | Valencia (Spain)

- Android development: Facebook friends quiz, sickness predictor, several speed reflex games.
- Development of booking platform for sport centers.
 - Keywords: Android, JavaScript, Java.
- Embedded device prototyping and development.
 Keywords: C, C++, CORTEX-M4, ANDROID, 3D Printing, Java.

CS

JUNIOR DEVELOPER Oct 2014 - Feb 2015 | Gdansk (Poland)

- Sales team support from the technical point of view.
- Technical presentations to potential customers.



EDUCATION

Oct 2021 – Jul 2023 MSC ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE'S RESEARCH - Specialty in reasoning and planning. Universidad Internacional Menéndez Pelayo (Spain)

Master's thesis: Satellite imaging analysis for invasive algae detection in the surface of lakes.

Feb 2017 - Mar 2018 SELF-DRIVING CAR NANODEGREE

The program contains the next topics: **Computer vision**, **deep learning**, **machine learning**, **sensor fusion**, **localization**, **control systems** and **path planning**.

It is focused on developing the necessary understanding and technical skills to create an autonomous vehicle able to drive safely in public roads.

2010-2014 **DEGREE IN INDUSTRIAL ELECTRONICS AND AUTOMATION ENGINEERING** - Specialty in embedded system and Real-Time computing. **Universitat Politècnica de València.** (Spain) Final thesis (A grade): Cross-platform Qt application for the automatic control of liquids tank. QML, C++

2014 SPRING SEMESTER ERASMUS SCHOLARSHIP

Faculty of Electrical Engineering. České vysoké učení technické v Praze. Prague (Czech Republic)

OTHER SIDE PROJECTS

- Telegram bot to detect and classify fish species from photos. Telegram API, Python, Tensorflow.
- Autonomous maritime drone. Raspberry Pi, C++, Python, Qt, QML, 3D modeling & printing.
- Vehicle detection & tracking with OpenCV and deep learning approaches. Python, OpenCV, Keras,
 Machine learning.
- Lane detection in the road using computer vision techniques. **Python, OpenCV.**
- Traffic sign identification and classification. Python, Tensorflow, OpenCV.